

Le Ngoc Truong An

Intern Front-end Developer

Date of birth: October 26, 1997

Gender: Male

Phone: 0332782244

Email: truongan261097@gmail.com

Address: Zone B Ho Chi Minh City National University,

Quarter 6, Linh Trung Town, Thu Duc District,

HCMC

Website: https://www.facebook.com/truong.an.35574406

OBJECTIVE

My short term goals are improving knowledge and skill such as ReactJS, ReactNative decentralized applications, after that build a real project to get experience.

My long term goal is to learn and work to become frontend developer expert. Keep learning another programming language like: NodeJS...

EDUCATION

2016 - 2020 Ho Chi Minh City University of Technology and Education

Major: Biomedical Electronics Engineer

WORK EXPERIENCE

2016 - 2020 Ho Chi Minh City University of Technology and Education

Student

2020 - Present CyberSoft Academy

Student

- Have knowledge Front-end:

• HTML5, CSS3 (Bootrap, SASS, LESS, FlexGrid)

Jquery

JavaScipt (ES6)

• ReactJS (Redux, Redux-Saga).

- Using git.

-Have knowledge OOP basic.

SKILLS

English	Reading and understanding english documents
Computer	Word, Excel, Powerpoint
Soft skills	Presentation, Team Work, Planing

INTERESTS

I like soccer, swim, boxing, painting..